Hello, everyone.
مرحبا جميعا.
Welcome back to our English listening practice.
مرحبا بعودتنا إلى ممارسة الاستماع للغة الإنجليزية.
How are you today?
كيف حالك اليوم؟
Are you feeling more confident in your English listening?
هل تشعر بثقة أكبر في استماعك للإنجليزية؟
I hope so.
آمل ذلك.
If you are still watching with subtitles,
إذا كنت لا تزال تشاهد مع ترجمة،
please turn them off now.
يرجى إيقافها الآن.
Try to listen carefully to what I say.
حاول أن تستمع جيدا لما أقول.
This will help you improve faster.
هذا سيساعدك على التحسن بشكل أسرع.
Write in the comments, what did you understand from
اكتب في التعليقات، ماذا فهمت من
today's story?
قصة اليوم؟
Today, I will tell you about my first day
اليوم، سأخبركم عن يومي الأول
at college in another country.
في الجامعة في بلد آخر.
It was a difficult day for me because
كان يوما صعبا بالنسبة لي لأن
everything was new.
كل شيء كان جديدا.
Have you ever studied in a different country or
هل سبق وأن درست في بلد مختلف أو
started at a new college?
بدأت في كلية جديدة؟
Have you felt nervous on your first day?
هل شعرت بالتوتر في يومك الأول؟
Sometimes, we don't know where to go.
أحيانا، لا نعرف إلى أين نذهب.
We don't know where our classroom is.
لا نعرف أين تقع صفنا.
So we need to ask for help.
لذا علينا أن نطلب المساعدة.
But can we understand that answer?
لكن هل يمكننا فهم هذا الجواب؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
In this video, you will learn how to ask
في هذا الفيديو، ستتعلم كيف تسأل
for help politely, how to speak clearly, and
للمساعدة بأدب، وكيفية التحدث بوضوح، و
how to feel more confident
كيف أشعر بثقة أكبر
on your first day at college.
في أول يوم لك في الجامعة.
I will speak slowly and clearly,
سأتحدث ببطء ووضوح
so you can follow easily.
لذا يمكنك المتابعة بسهولة.
Are you ready?
هل أنت مستعد؟